

MARTYNAS ČIŽAS

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER ♥ VILNIUS, LITHUANIA +37065815526

• PERSONAL DETAILS: •

Vilnius Lithuania +37065815526

martynas.cizas.webdev@gmail.com

Date of birth 1991/10/29

SKILLS:

HTML5 / CSS3

JavaScript

React.js / Express.js / Node.js

SQL

OOP

NPM Git

Visual Studio Code

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

<u>GitHub</u>

<u>Facebook</u>

Personal Web

HOBBIES

Write some code, swimming, running, ride a bike, exercise in gym, music, driving.

• LANGUAGES •

Lithuanian

English

Russian

ABOUT ME:

More than eight years of working as swimming coach, I strive to change my career road to IT. I'm learning every day, and giving all my effort. My new horizon and dream is to become an excellent programmer.

I'm Responsible, punctual, focused on detail, got good logical thinking.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:

Swimming Coach at "Sveikas Miestas", Vilnius

January 2019 — Present

Swimming Coach at "Impuls LTU", Vilnius

May 2013 — January 2021

INTERNSHIPS (IT):

Front - End developer at www.codebakers.lt, Vilnius

August 2018 — November 2018

Project (Teamwork): CodeBakers kids react.js + node.js + express.js. Creating RESTful APIs on the server side. React.js - Data retrieval from the server and rendering. Front-end we used SASS / SCSS for work.

Simple cms - react + redux + firebase. The full wheel application, that was being created using react.js + redux. Application with multi-level user interfaces (guest, user, administrator). Data Storage in NoSQL Database Firebase. Utilization of MVVM structure by react.js binding to Firebase. Git.

EDUCATION:

Master, Lithuanian University of Educational Sciences, Vilnius

September 2014 - May 2016

Master Degree of Science in Physical Education and Sports

Bachelor, Lithuanian University of Educational Sciences, Vilnius

 $September\,2010-May\,2014$

Bachelor Degree in Sports / Teacher Qualification of Physical Education

COURSES:

Ultimate Web Designer & Developer Course (40hrs, udemy.com), www.udemy.com January 2018 — August 2018

Advanced Front - End development course (240hrs, in 4 people team), www.codebakers.lt

August 2018 — November 2018

Complete Web Developer: zero to master (40hrs, udemy.com), www.udemy.com December 2019 — June 2020